What's wrong with her?
她有什麼事啊
My abdomen hurts
肚子好痛
abdomen
肚子
What can she do
她能怎樣
Aren't you just pretending to be dead?
不就是在裝死
There are outsiders here
這有外人在
Don't embarrass yourself here
你別在這丟人現眼了
Ambulance
救護車
She does not have the conditions for a natural birth
她不具備自然產的條件
No
不行
I firmly disagree with caesarean section
我堅決不同意剖腹產
If you don't sign, your life will be in danger.
再不簽字就有生命危險了
Don't sign if your life is in danger
有生命危險也不簽
I strongly disagree
我堅決不同意
Even if she dies
就算她死
I also want to give birth to my grandson naturally.
也要把我的孫子順產下來
This is her blessing
這是她的福氣
Can I sign it myself?
我能自己簽名嗎
Don't stop me
別攔著我
Do you dare to sign for me?
你敢簽字
If you sign, I will strangle you to death.
你簽字我就掐死你
Preparing for surgery
準備手術